realisationpar.com 2019-05-20

# Privacy

## RealisationPar.com Privacy Policy

Realisation Par Limited, a Hong Kong Private Company limited by shares and each of its subsidiaries and affiliates (“Realisation Par”) respects your privacy and wants you to understand our privacy policy. This Privacy Policy page communicates how, when, and why we gather information about our customers and what we do with it.

Realisation Par reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. By accessing www.realisationpar.com (“Website”), you confirm that you have read and understand this policy including how and why we use your information. If you don’t want us to collect or use your personal information, you should not use the Website or order goods from Realisation Par. We are not responsible for the content or privacy policies of third parties.

## Website Security

We have taken many precautions to protect confidential information while you shop using the Website. We use the industry-standard SSL protocol (Secure Sockets Layer) to secure credit card transactions. The SSL system encrypts information that you submit to us via our website when you place an order as a safeguard against third party interception of your information.

## IP Address

To facilitate a smooth shopping experience, our system logs the Internet Protocol (IP) Address of each user. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer every time you browse the internet. Depending on your Internet Service Provider (ISP) and the type of connection, this number may change each time you log on. Information from IP addresses is used for system administration, our live help feature, troubleshooting, and the examination of traffic trends and response rates to various promotional offers. This data is used in the aggregate, and is not linked to personally identifiable information.

## Gathering and Use of Your Personally Identifiable Information

If you place an order through Realisation Par, we will ask you for your name, email address, shipping address, telephone number and part of your credit card information. We use this information to process and fulfil your order and to notify you of your order status. Telephone numbers and e-mail addresses are used to contact you regarding your order. Alternatively you may request to receive our e-mail newsletter updates.

We collect information from you when you visit our site including your IP address or unique device identifier, and cookies and data from the pages you visit. This is stored in log files and used to provide you more pertinent content when you visit our site. Your IP address, when available is used to provide a localied experience including prices in your currency and to adhere to regional preferences and requirements.  

 “Cookies” are used by every website. “Cookies” are small text files placed by a website on the web browser of a user who lands on a web page, then reads the information collected every time a user performs a function. We use cookies to provide security to you and assist in navigating the Website.  Refer below to learn more about our specific uses of cookies and for information on how to opt out.

## Third Party

Facebook (Facebook Custom Audience)

Google (AdWords Remarketing)

Google (Google Analytics)

## Type of cookies

### Interest-based Advertising

This cookie allows us to target the advertising we do on Facebook more effectively by matching data we hold with that held by Facebook.

### Interest-based Advertising

This cookie facilitates post-visit messaging to drive return visits.

### Analytics

This cookie provides anonymised data to allow us to understand user behaviour and marketing performance of Realisation Par.

## More information and how to opt out

 HYPERLINK "http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/" \t "_blank"  
http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/

HYPERLINK "https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated?hl=en" \t "_blank"  
https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated?hl=en

HYPERLINK "https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout" \t "_blank"  
https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout

## BigCommerce (our ecommerce platform)

**Analytics.  **This cookie provides anonymised data to allow us to understand user behaviour and marketing performance of RealisationPar and also to assist in the website experience for the user See:HYPERLINK "http://www.aboutcookies.org/" \t "_blank" aboutcookies.org. You can delete all cookies that are already on your computer and you can set most browsers to prevent them from being placed.

We use your personal information to improve and customise our services, including sharing of your information for such purposes. This includes uses which we intend to provide an optimal match between you and our available products and services, including direct marketing. Such uses serve our interest in improving and growing our business and your interest in receiving optimal user results.  

We use your personal information for security and safety purposes, including our own use and with third party security providers. We aim to protect you and us from spam, harassment, intellectual property infringement, crime and other security risks. We use personal information to comply with legal obligations pursuant to the legal protections afforded to you in your country. Where required to obey the law, such as in response to a subpoena or legal process we will disclose your personal information. We also reserve the right to use your personal information to exercise or defend legal claims.

We use your personal information to engage third party companies and individuals to provide services to us (such as payment processors, research companies, and analytics and security providers) to help us operate, provide and market our products and services. We use third parties where necessary or where their services are superior to what we could perform internally. 

We will only retain your information for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this policy or as needed to provide services to you or to advertise or market services to you. If you do not use our Website or order goods from us for 7 years (from the date of your most recent order), we will delete your personal information with certain exceptions. For example, we may not delete your personal information insofar as it is needed to uphold our legal obligations, resolve disputes, or enforce our agreements.

If you would like to modify your information on file with us, request deletion of data, or terminate your account, please contact talktomebaby@realisationpar.com

## Email List

When you sign up for our email newsletters, we ask for your first name and email address. If you do not wish to receive our email anymore, an unsubscribe button is located at the bottom of each email for your convenience. You can also unsubscribe by contacting talktomebaby@realisationpar.com.

## Online Tracking

Website uses Google Analytics and may be able to see user’s referring site. Website does not respond to “do not track” signals, though users may be able to provide tracking instructions to Google Analytics. To opt out of Google Analytics, visit the Google Analytics opt-out page found at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout and install the add-on for your browser. For more details on installing and uninstalling the add-on, please see the relevant help resources for your specific browser

## GDPR Compliance

Realisation Par complies with the requirements of the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) with respect to data concerning citizens or residents of European Union countries and Switzerland. To the extent other terms of this Privacy Policy or Realisation Par’s Terms and Conditions contradict the terms herein as applied to EU Residents and Citizens, the terms of this “GDPR Compliance” section control.

EU residents and citizens have the following eight rights under GDPR and are entitled to the facilitation of these rights by Realisation Par as set forth herein:

### Right to be Informed

Realisation Par collects the following “personal information” as defined in GDPR when a sale is consummated: name, e-mail address, shipping address, telephone number and partial credit card information. We use this information to process and fulfil your order and to notify you of your order status. You may also choose to provide us with your personal information of varied nature if you contact us regarding customer service concerns.

### Right of Access

EU residents and citizens have a right to be informed of data that is stored, processed or analysed and to obtain a copy in plain English. To request such information please email us at talktomebaby@realisationpar.com.using the same email you used to complete your transaction and provide us with your payment information in order to provide your account security.

### Right to Rectification

EU residents and citizens have a right to revise our information if inaccurate or complete, and if information is disclosed to third parties to have that information rectified by the third parties. If after accessing your information, an EU resident or citizen believes our information on file regarding you is inaccurate, one may respond to the email which was provided with information pursuant to EU resident or citizen right of access and provide the rectifying information.

### Right of Erasure

This is a non-absolute ‘right to be forgotten.’ If you are an EU resident or citizen and after accessing your information you would like to have it erased, please send an email explaining the circumstances warranting erasure to the email which provided your information pursuant to your right of access. We may comply with the request, we may have a legal obligation to preserve some or all data under relevant laws, and/or we may have a legal right to retain information you have requested be deleted. You will be advised of our decision regarding your data erasure request.

**Right to Portability of Data.** EU residents and citizens have a right to have your data stored with us to be moved, copied or transported in a safe and secure manner without affecting its usability. If you would like your personal data in portable form, please email a request to talktomebaby@realisationpar.com.with the subject line “Request for portable data”

### Right to Object to Processing

EU subjects may object to direct marketing including including any personalised website content, emails, or to all processing of their personal information. EU citizens and residents have an absolute right to object to use of their personal data for direct marketing purposes. You may not have an absolute right to object if your personal data is used for a task carried out in the public interest, or for legitimate interests such as scientific or historical research or statistical purposes. If you are an EU citizen or resident who objects to processing of their personal information, please send an email request to talktomebaby@realisationpar.com.with the subject line “Objection to processing” and tell us whether you object to direct marketing or all processing.

### Rights in Relation to Automated Decision-making

Realisation Par uses personal information to profile customers including to facilitate direct marketing. Realisation Par may also provide emails, marketing, or advertising to EU citizens or subjects by automated means, and automated (non-human) responses to customer actions or requests. If you would like more information regarding Realisation Par’s automated decision-making or to request human follow up to an automated promotion or Realisation Par’s communication, or a response to an EU citizen or resident action or request, please send an email request to talktomebaby@realisationpar.com.with the subject line “Automated decision making” and provide the details of the transaction in question.

### Privacy Policy Changes

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we believe the changes are material, we will let you know by one or more of the following: (1) posting a conspicuous notice on the Website or (2) sending you an email regarding the changes.

This privacy policy is published and takes effect January 14th, 2019.
